<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>metaverse NFT &#8211; techsarpss</title>
	<atom:link href="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/tag/metaverse-nft/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What is metaverse? How metaverse technology will change the world</title>
		<link>https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/what-is-metaverse/</link>
					<comments>https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/what-is-metaverse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AmitRpandey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[technical news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual world]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[What is metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techsarp.com/?p=1622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[metaverse technology: Friends, do you know what metaverse is and how it works in the world, what is its technology? Friends, the metaverse is told about a fictional world connected to a real world, whatever work will be done in this world, it will be the best of all our technology. How does the metaverse [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>metaverse technology:</strong> Friends, do you know what metaverse is and how it works in the world, what is its technology? Friends, the metaverse is told about a fictional world connected to a real world, whatever work will be done in this world, it will be the best of all our technology. How does the metaverse work, what are its features, let&#8217;s understand it in detail below.</p>



<p>Friends, it is hardly possible for anyone to jump from the heights of 30 thousand feet without a parachute and to remain alive even after being shot many times, but such technology has come, and even after all this, no harm can be done to you.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img decoding="async" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-is-metaverse1-1024x624.webp" alt="What is metaverse1.webp" class="wp-image-1690" width="709" height="433" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-is-metaverse1-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-is-metaverse1-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-is-metaverse1-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-is-metaverse1.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 100vw, 709px" /></figure>



<p>Rather you can do a world tour sitting in the USA and go anywhere and attend any events and parties or meetings and take their experience and all this will be possible with VR Yes, friends VR i.e. virtual reality is a world from which we can feel virtually but it does not exist in reality.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://techsarp.com/digital-marketing-kaise-karen/">Read also….Digital marketing क्या है? कितने प्रकार के होते हैं?</a></strong></p>



<h2><strong>What is metaverse?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>metaverse</strong> <strong>virtual reality</strong>: Friends, some names in the character of <strong>Harry Potter</strong> detective <strong>novels</strong> are <strong>James Bond</strong>, <strong>Solo Holmes, Karamchand</strong> is famous today, they have no real existence but in fantasy folk, it is so famous that it will feel like it is around you in the <strong>15th century</strong> by <strong>Leonardo</strong> da Bansi When the picture of the airplane was made, it was not visible anywhere.</p>



<p>Similarly, <strong>Jules Verne</strong> made a fictional picture of a submarine on his <strong>book</strong> in the <strong>18th century</strong>, when no one could think of submarines, similar fictional characters were created by intellectuals and they became famous.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img decoding="async" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse-1024x624.webp" alt="What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse.webp" class="wp-image-1691" width="702" height="428" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-can-you-do-in-Metaverse.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 702px) 100vw, 702px" /></figure>



<p>Similarly, in<strong> 1992</strong>, a novel called Snow Crash was <strong>authored</strong> by Neal Stephenson, he first gave us the word metaverse, the way we imagine that there is something that is omnipotent, omnipresent, in the same way, <strong>Neal Stephenson</strong> did something like this. It was imagined in the<strong> year 1992</strong> that wherever a person is sitting, his picture should reach the other corner of the world.</p>



<p>There was no internet then, to say in a pure language, this technology was not so developed and today images reach from one corner to another and you can send photos anywhere in the world, you can also make video calls.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://techsarp.com/cryptocurrency-kya-hai/">Read also….cryptocurrency kya hai और उसके क्या क्या फायदे और नुकसान हैं जाने</a></strong></p>



<h2><strong>What is metaverse</strong>? <strong>How does Metaverse work?</strong></h2>



<p><br><strong>What is metaverse</strong>: But when talking about the metaverse, it is said that you can roam around the world even by staying at home. And you can be seen walking anywhere, do not understand, let&#8217;s assume you are in <strong>Delhi</strong> and you want to go to a meeting in <strong>America</strong>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="624" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/How-does-Metaverse-work-1024x624.webp" alt="How-does-Metaverse-work.webp" class="wp-image-1692" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/How-does-Metaverse-work-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/How-does-Metaverse-work-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/How-does-Metaverse-work-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/How-does-Metaverse-work.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>So you will reach <strong>America</strong> meeting from <strong>Delhi</strong> through a <strong>3D dimensional</strong> image and you can also talk with your partner by sitting there. Friends, like you, have to buy something and you are at your home, you go to any shop in America through 3D dimensional and see and like the things there and book it online and that stuff will get you there. It automatically comes to your home through 3D Dimensional without going.</p>



<p>As this process became common, it was found that now there would be no need for visas and passports to go from one country to another in the world, this <strong>technology</strong> has been named Metaverse.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://techsarp.com/paypal-account-kaise-banaen/">Read also&#8230;.paypal account kaise banaen जाने आसान तरीका</a></strong></p>



<h2><strong>What can you do in Metaverse?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>virtual reality:</strong> We will tell you what we can do in this virtual reality, how it is turning every reality virtual experience in the world into virtual, and why now Facebook is entering the world of metaverse through chatting and different meta than setting and uploading.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="624" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse-1024x624.webp" alt="Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse.webp" class="wp-image-1693" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Impact-on-the-world-from-the-metaverse.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Friends, <strong>Virtual Reality</strong> <strong>VR</strong> is a type of experience that can be experienced only with the help of computer software and hardware gadgets. VR is such a 3D computer-created world that you can feel both mentally and physically, but we can feel the vibe of this virtual reality with both our senses, eyes and Ear, which requires wearing a head-mounted <strong>hardware</strong> <strong>gadget </strong>and Sensor gloves in the hands which are connected.</p>



<p>From a powerful computer where your real-time experience is created in detail through an amazing world of software and it is so much detail that you can enjoy it completely like the real world. Now <strong>Facebook</strong> is also setting its foot in the virtual world of Metaverse named Meta, where they are planning the next level feature, which will rule the world of VR in the <strong>virtual world</strong> in the coming time.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/amitrpandeyarp/">Follow on Instagram</a></strong></p>



<h2><strong>Impact on the world from the metaverse</strong></h2>



<p><strong>metaverse projects:</strong> You are opening VR parks in many places in the world, where you can have a real-time experience of your imaginary world in a closed room or you can also say that it is converting real experience into virtual. So, first of all, let&#8217;s talk about Amusement Park friends, whether he am a child or all adults who go to the amusement park to fill their day with adventure, where various activities like swings and water slides are available.</p>



<p>But in the coming times, all these things may not be seen in real.<br>Because now it has become possible to do all these adventures even in a closed room, whether it is a water slide or every adventure of a dangerous stand amusement park will now be possible only with VR, which you will see in malls nowadays.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="624" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse-1024x624.webp" alt="what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse.webp" class="wp-image-1694" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/what-is-new-feature-of-metaverse.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Real-life adventure:</strong> Friends, there are many such real life adventures that require courage to do because there is a danger of life in it such as punching jumping from mountain clip, free pole from sky height, river rafting or mountain biking all these things. It takes a strong heart and practice to do.</p>



<p>Now even children are enjoying all these <strong>adventures</strong>, but not in real but through virtual reality, in the same way as playing VR video games, in the same way, the experience is done in the VR park, which you can hear and watch along with- Along with this, we also do physical experience.</p>



<h2></h2>



<p><strong>Life event:</strong> Friends, this technology is being made so hi-tech that you will be able to attend live events from music concerts, play exhibitions, that too some such life events are in Mumbai and you are in Goa and not only this but your friends are sitting in Delhi and Bangalore. Can also participate in this.</p>



<p>Along with this, now you will be able to enjoy the fun of traveling sitting at home, as soon as you press a switch, you will go to roam the streets of Paris and sometimes you will be enjoying the luxury cruise ship running in the sea.</p>



<p>In <strong>virtual reality</strong>, not only entertainment, but students can also do their studies, just have to put this equipment which looks like glasses on their eyes and they will understand everything through 3D animation as if it is happening in front of them.</p>



<p>Friends, the world is moving fast at the speed of bullets, and with that new technology is coming every day, so if you do not stay updated then you will be left behind.</p>



<p><strong>metaverse Facebook:</strong> Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg does not like to be behind, you know that whatever social media became popular, he went on joining Facebook, and added a few friends on Facebook so that there would be no competition recently. The Facebook company changed the name of Facebook to <strong>Meta Facebook</strong>.</p>



<h2><strong>How Metaverse will become the world&#8217;s business platforms</strong></h2>



<p><strong>Metaverse</strong> <strong>platforms</strong>: The Metaverse will be a virtual world In this world of augmented reality we will all have a virtual image of the way we buy equipment and different clothes for our characters in the gaming world. In the same way, in the world of the Metaverse, people will spend money to improve clothes, shoes and hairstyles for their counterparts, similarly people will also be present on the Metaverse who will offer the service of selling clothes to people&#8217;s <strong>digital avatars</strong> and repairing hairstyles.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="624" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse-1024x624.webp" alt="What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse.webp" class="wp-image-1700" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-are-the-benefits-of-metaverse.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Metaverse</strong> <strong>NFT</strong>: In such a situation, Metaverse is also a very big business platform for the people, many big brands of clothes and shoes are about to enter the world of Metaverse, soon their virtual shops will come on this platform. On Metaverse, you will be able to buy these things with the help of <strong>NFT (non-fungible token)</strong>, so on one hand many people will take advantage of the services on all this platform and on the other hand many people will earn a lot of money by selling these services.</p>



<p>On Metaverse, you will also be able to be a part of business meetings with your digital avatar, you and your colleagues will be in a virtual form, you will be able to meet with them. Apart from this, you will also be able to work with your office colleagues on the Metaverse platform. You will get a great experience while working on the Metaverse. In this advanced technology world, you will be able to experience working in mountains or rivers and other virtual beautiful places with the rest of the employees.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://techsarp.com/singapore-me-job-kaise-paye-%e0%a4%b8%e0%a4%bf%e0%a4%82%e0%a4%97%e0%a4%be%e0%a4%aa%e0%a5%81%e0%a4%b0-%e0%a4%ae%e0%a5%87%e0%a4%82-%e0%a4%a8%e0%a5%8c%e0%a4%95%e0%a4%b0%e0%a5%80/">Read also&#8230;..सिंगापुर में नौकरी job कैसे पाए जाने तरीके</a></strong></p>



<h2><strong>What are the benefits and disadvantages of the metaverse?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>disadvantages</strong>: 1- Friends, in today&#8217;s date, social media mobile is needed by everyone, everyone has got an addiction and it has become a habit and with the advent of metaverse, that habit will increase even more.</p>



<p>2- Getting lost in the virtual world will bring a lot of change in your own nature, the way normally we go out, meet people and keep learning something and because of this virtual reality, you people cannot get out. Due to this there can be changes in your nature as well.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="624" src="http://techsarp.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse-1024x624.webp" alt="What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse.webp" class="wp-image-1695" srcset="https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse-1024x624.webp 1024w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse-300x183.webp 300w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse-768x468.webp 768w, https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/What-would-be-the-harm-of-the-metaverse.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>3- Friends, physically you will also have many side effects from this, when everything will become digital and virtual and your coming out and walking, which is an enjoyment, will have a lot of effect on it.</p>



<p>4- Friends, there will be a lot of impact on your privacy, when Metaverse will give you any facility for its own meaning, it will definitely use your data and privacy for itself somewhere. In today&#8217;s date there are many online websites where your data resides there But she uses that data for her own meaning somewhere, you must have heard this kind of news a lot.</p>



<h2></h2>



<p>5- When you start living a <strong>virtual life</strong>, then all the benefits you get from nature will end, when we live in <strong>digital life</strong>, then our power conversion will become more, its effect will be on our nature.</p>



<p>6- Friends, after the arrival of the metaverse, humans will start being limited in themselves, people will be connected to each other virtually, not meeting each other in reality.</p>



<p>7- Due to this, most people will be left alone, when the metaverse progresses, during that time humans may forget to differentiate between the real and the virtual world.</p>



<p>8- Due to being alone for a long time, a person will suffer from many types of mental diseases like depression.</p>



<p><strong>benefits</strong>: 1- Friends, when a person does a work for a long time, then he starts feeling harassed while doing that work, but after the arrival of the metaverse, he will do that work well and there will be no harasse.</p>



<p>2- Friends, without going to school, you will be able to talk to all the friends and teachers of the school sitting at home and you can get all the information about your studies sitting at home.</p>



<p>3- Friends, if you want to go to a meeting or roam anywhere, then you can meet and roam through the <strong>virtual world</strong> sitting at home.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://techsarp.com/%e0%a4%9c%e0%a5%80%e0%a4%ac%e0%a5%80-%e0%a4%b5%e0%a5%8d%e0%a4%b9%e0%a4%be%e0%a4%9f%e0%a5%8d%e0%a4%b8%e0%a4%8f%e0%a4%aa-what-is-gb-whatsapp/">Read more&#8230;&#8230;</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://techsarp.github.io/techsarp/what-is-metaverse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
